{
    "id": "a576f94295da488e88c9f3d3bd6499ff",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Arthritis is a common complaint ……………………….. the elderly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "between",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Did she confide her plans …………………………. you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Diplomas were conferred ………………………… members of the graduating class.",
            "description": "confer + on",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The bank manager has complete confidence ……………………….. the tellers.",
            "description": "confidence + in",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Please confine your remarks …………………………. the topic under discussion.",
            "description": "confine + to",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I congratulate you ……………………………. your twentieth anniversary.",
            "description": "congratulate + on",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You confused me …………………………… my twin brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Were you conscious …………………………… his hostility?",
            "description": "conscious + of",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a bitter contest ………………………….. wills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We must be prepared …………………………… any contingency.",
            "description": "prepared + for",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Whether the picnic is held or not is dependent ………………………….. the weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Lying is contrary …………………………….. my beliefs.",
            "description": "contrary + to",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}